Jackie Martin Papers
Jackie Martin Papers
- Projects and assignments
  - United States Information Agency (USIA), Federal Services, 1950-1957
    - USIA telephone directories, 1960-1961; approximately 80 photographs in this section (Box 18)
- Subject files
  - Presidents and leaders
    - Bradley, Omar (General)
      - Speeches, 1949-1955 (Box 18)
    - Churchill, Winston, 12 Dec 1941-01 Jan 1942; Volumes 1-3 were originally in scrapbook form
      - Volume 1: Photo assignment in Ottawa for the Chicago Sun (Box 18)
      - Volume 1: Correspondence and notes (Box 18)
      - Volume 2: "A Night To Remember: New Year's Eve With Winston Churchill in ", 1942 (Box 18)
      - Volume 2: Manuscripts and notes, correspondence (Box 18)
      - Volume 2: Clippings of "A Night To Remember" (Box 18)
      - Volume 3: "A Private Memorial To a Great Man" (Box 18)
      - Volume 3: Clippings (Box 18)
      - Manuscript, "A Night To Remember", 1942 (Box 18)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight
      - Inauguration 1952; "State of the Union" address with photographs 1958 (Box 18)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 18)
      - Photographs with Joe Collins, PAR #2542 (Box 18)
      - Newspapers, 1945 (Box 18)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B.
      - Convention in Atlantic City; "The Great Society" with photograph, 1964 (Box 19)
      - Speeches and inauguration (Box 19)
      - Return to Texas; Nixon's inauguration, 1969 (Box 19)
    - Kennedy, John F.
      - JFK record, acceptance speech ( 1960); Robert F. Kennedy's convention speech ( 1964) (Box 19)
      - List of women leaders (Box 19)
      - Clippings, 1960-1963 (Box 19)
      - Kennedy-Nixon campaign, 1960 (Box 19)
    - Kennedy, Robert F.
      - Clippings (Box 19)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D. and Eleanor Roosevelt
      - Photographs (Box 19)
      - Roosevelt Library, Hyde Park, N.Y. (Box 19)
      - Clippings (Box 19)
      - Correspondence, 1937-1955 (Box 19)
    - Truman, Harry
      - Photographs of family (Box 19)
      - Clippings, 1982; 1946-1949 (Box 19)
      - Correspondence, 1945-1965; approximately 110 photographs in this section (Box 19)
  - General
    - Advertising Club dedication prophecies for 2004 - written in 1948 (Box 19)
    - Brussels: International Women's Day march (Box 19)
    - Business directories (Box 19)
    - Communications media, 3 folders; See also Financial records: Office 1959-1969: "TELE-News Now" proposal 1963 (Box 19)
    - Communism, clippings (Box 19)
    - Computer programming (Box 19)
    - Department of State directories (Box 19)
    - Diplomatic lists, 1958-1968 (Box 19)
    - Electronics (Box 19)
    - Flea Market, "Vive la Flea Market" by Madeline Rose (Box 19)
    - Foreign countries
      - Commerce; Commerce and communication; Government (Box 20)
      - Commerce and communication (Box 20)
      - Government (Box 20)
    - Foreign policy/aid clippings, 1960-1968 (Box 20)
    - Foreign Service Institute, 1962 (Box 20)
    - Health insurance (Box 20)
    - Hungary: East Europe affairs, 1956-1957 (Box 20)
    - International Labor Organization, Lee Stanley (Box 20)
    - International organizations (Box 20)
    - "Invasion Remembered: 1954", 3 folders (Box 20)
    - Labor organizations: labor union directories (Box 20)
    - Newspaper layout sheets, dummies (Box 20)
    - Newspaper sales: papers die, combine, are bought, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
    - Poland: Women's National Party (Box 20)
    - Potomac River Power Sqaudron: William Pugh, 1944 (Box 20)
    - Prices: photographic equipment information, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Prices: other than photographic (Box 21)
    - Reading Dynamics Institute (Box 21)
    - Rio Grande Estates, 1961-1963 (Box 21)
    - Telephone directories (Box 21)
    - Travel information: Pennsylvannia Dutch expo, 1967 (Box 21)
    - United States Government, See also Financial records: Office 1959-1969: "TELE-News Now" proposal 1963
      - Executive branch (Box 21)
      - Executive branch (Box 21)
      - Independent agencies (Box 21)
      - Independent agencies (Box 21)
      - Judicial branch (Box 21)
      - Legislative, Senate (Box 21)
      - Legislative, the House (Box 21)
      - Legislative phone directories (Box 21)
      - Publications price booklets (Box 21)
    - Washington D.C.
      - Guide and national landmarks (Box 21)
      - Organizations' directories and rosters (Box 21)
      - Museums, galleries, and national parks (Box 21)
      - Universities and colleges (Box 21)
- Memorabilia
  - Organizations and clubs, Autobiographical/biographical
    - Delta Gamma (DG)
      - Correspondence
        - From Leland Publishers, 1965-1966 (Box 22)
        - To Jackie Martin, 1960-1968 (Box 22)
        - Frats to Jackie Martin, 1963-1964 (Box 22)
        - From Jackie Martin, 1963-1964 (Box 22)
        - Interoffice, 1963-1964 (Box 22)
      - Notes (Box 22)
      - "Jackie Martin Receives Rose Award," clippings and correspondence, 1962 (Box 22)
      - Manuscript, Jackie Martin "Meets with Collegiates", 1963 (Box 22)
      - "Anchora" coverage of schools (Box 22)
      - Mrs. Abernethy's letter of recommendation of Jackie Martin (Box 22)
      - Memorabilia, sorority, 1960-1968 (Box 22)
      - Clippings from office to Jackie Martin (Box 22)
      - Publicity flyer, Anchora Exhibit Display designed by Jackie Martin (Box 22)
      - Background file, Anchora Exhibit Display with Steve Kellog (Box 22)
      - Roughs of panels for Anchora Exhibit Display (Box 22)
      - Background file (Box 22)
      - Background file, pledge/hand books, 1950-1968 (Box 22)
      - Booklets, National Panhellenic Conference, 1958-1963 (Box 22)
      - Anchora Magazine, 1955; 1959,; 1963-1968; quarterly; 6 folders (Box 22)
    - American Newspaper Women's Club (ANWC), newsletter "Shop Talk"
      - ANWC annual membership rosters (Box 23)
      - ANWC correspondence (Box 23)
    - DACOR House (Box 23)
    - Daughters of the American Revolution (DAR) (Box 23)
    - National Press Club (NPC) (Box 23)
    - National Press Photographer's Association (NPPA) (Box 23)
    - Overseas Press Club (OPC) Bulletin, 1964-1967
      - OPC correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 23)
    - The Royal Photographic Society (RPS) of Great Britain (Box 23)
    - Theta Sigma Phi, correspondence, 1948 (Box 23)
    - Washington Newspaper Guild, correspondence (Box 23)
    - Womens Newspaper Guild, correspondence (Box 23)
    - Womens National Democratic Club (WNDC), correspondence, 1967 (Box 23)
    - Womens National Press Club (WNPC)
      - WNPC, Times-Herald tearsheets about annual stunt party, 1929-1936 (Box 23)
    - White House News Photographers Association (WHNPA) (Box 23)
  - Clippings
    - Adenauer, Konrad, 1963-1967 (Box 23)
    - Arts and entertainment, 1960-1968 (Box 23)
    - Atlantic charter (Box 23)
    - Britain: the Thaw; common market, 1966-1967 (Box 23)
    - Concerts/music/theater, 1947-1948 (Box 23)
    - Education, 1967-1969 (Box 23)
    - Finance/business/industry, 1960-1963 (Box 23)
    - Foundation Publisher's Press, 1965-1966 (Box 23)
    - French Revolt, Degaulle, 1965-1967 (Box 23)
    - Germany: Atomic Role; Kiesinger and the Thaw, 1966-1967 (Box 23)
    - Grosvenor, Gilbert; National Geographic Society (Box 23)
    - Martin Luther King Jr. assassination, 1968 (Box 23)
    - Law, 1967-1969 (Box 23)
    - Lippman, Walter, Washington Post column, 1960-1967 (Box 23)
    - McNamara, James, 1967 (Box 23)
    - Military insignia (Box 23)
    - Newspapers "Die, combine and are bought", 1966 (Box 24)
    - Obituaries, 1960-1968 (Box 24)
    - O Globo Rio newspaper, 1966 (Box 24)
    - Popes encyclicals, 1960-1969 (Box 24)
    - Programs (Box 24)
    - Riots and student revolts, 1968 (Box 24)
    - Science "the brain drain", 1962-1967 (Box 24)
    - SHAPE-NATO, 1965-1968 (Box 24)
    - Ski vacation, 1967 (Box 24)
    - Stationery (Box 24)
    - Stevenson, Adlai, 1965-1968 (Box 24)
    - Tonkin Bay, 1960-1966 (Box 24)
    - Travel and interest, 1960-1968 (Box 24)
    - Treasured letters and photographs (Box 24)
    - Truman Doctrine, 1946-1947; 1967 (Box 24)
    - 20 Years after V-E and D-day, 1964-1967 (Box 24)
    - United Nations, 1960; 1967 (Box 24)
    - U.S.- European monetary, 1960-1968 (Box 24)
    - USSR invades Czechoslavakia, 1960-1968 (Box 24)
    - Vietnam/Asia, 1965-1968 (Box 24)
    - Vikingland trip, 1949; 5 folders (Box 24)
    - Washington government, 1947-1948 (Box 25)
    - "Washington Riot", 1968 (Box 25)
    - "The World Changes", 1967 (Box 25)
    - World War II, 1940-1947; 1960-1967; 9 folders (Box 25)
    - World War II: Special Editions "Nazi's Surrender!", 1945 (Box 25)
    - World War II: Germany/Hitler/Nazis, 1944-1947; 1960s (Box 25)
    - World War II: memorabilia (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 25)
  - Maps
    - Map to Pugh family cottage at Edgewater, Maryland (Box 26)
    - War boundries: Theater of War, 01 Sep 1939 (Box 26)
    - Army war maps
      - Europe roads, 1943 (Box 26)
      - Germany roads, 1943 (Box 26)
      - Italy roads, 1943 (Box 26)
      - Italy roads, 1943 (Box 26)
      - Air-routes, 1943-1945 (Box 26)
    - Michelin tourist maps
      - Europe, 1943-1945 (Box 26)
      - French, 1943-1945 (Box 26)
      - Germany, Austria, Hungary, 1943-1945 (Box 26)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 26)
    - Afrique: French possession and colonies, 1940 (Box 26)
    - Arctic region, 4 quadrants: Alaska, Asia, Greenland, Europe (Box 26)
    - Brussels (Box 26)
    - Denmark, England, Finland, Egypt, and travel guides (Box 26)
    - Europe, Asia, Germany (Box 26)
    - Europe and Near East, 1949-1965 (Box 26)
    - France/Paris/Lyons/Chartres, 1943-1949 (Box 26)
    - France: Herald-Tribune guides for France and Italy, 1952-1954 (Box 26)
    - French regions, brochures (Box 26)
    - Germany, Austria, Rhine, Belgium (Box 26)
    - Invasion, 1944 (Box 26)
    - Netherlands, Norway, Holland, Italy, Greece (Box 26)
    - The Pacific, 1943 (Box 27)
    - South America, See also Memorabilia: Scrapbooks: Brazil (Volume 3) for map of Brazil (Box 27)
    - Sweden, Turkey, Yugoslavia (Box 27)
    - Switzerland (Box 27)
    - United States and Washington D.C. area (Box 27)
    - World maps, 1932; 1935,; 1941,; 1965 (Box 27)
    - European inland waterways (Box 27)
    - The Heavens (Box 27)
    - U.S.S. Liberty, Ship deck plans (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous maps (Box 27)
  - Audiorecordings
    - John F. Kennedy: the President Years: 1960-63, martin_cj_001; Phonograph record (Box 50)
    - Captain Steichen on the “Family of Man”, 07/11/1955; martin_cj_002; “Family of Man” was an exhibit curated by Steichen at the Museum of Modern Art in NYC. Here he is speaking on the exhibit.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - JFK: May 29, 1917 - November 22, 1963, martin_cj_003; Documentary about John F. Kennedy. Narrated by Barry Gray, edited by Richard Sloan,; Phonograph record (Box 50)
    - John F. Kennedy: A Memorial Album: Inauguration January 20, 1961, martin_cj_004; Phonograph record (Box 50)
    - [untitled, labeled I and II], martin_cj_005; Phonograph record (Box 50)
    - [untitled, labeled III and 4], martin_cj_006; Phonograph record (Box 50)
    - Acceptence Speech: Nomination by the Democratic Party, 07/16/1960; martin_cj_007; Speech by senator John F. Kennedy accepting Democratic Party nomination for president.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - Let Us Begin, 01/20/1961; martin_cj_008; Inauguration ceremonies, John F. Kennedy.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - JFK Addresses Class at American University; Washington on Cold War, 06/11/1963; martin_cj_009; President John F. Kennedy addresses a college class (possibly a commencement ceremony?); talks about Cold War; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - Missiles in Cuba, 10/22/1962; martin_cj_010; John F. Kennedy discusses Cuban Missile Crisis; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - Edited Senator JFK Acceptance Speech at L.A., 07/16/1960; martin_cj_011; Senator John F. Kennedy gives acceptance speech for Democratic Presidential nomination; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - “I am Ready” Senator JFK press conference, martin_cj_012; John F. Kennedy press conference, location unknown; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - RFK Buried at St. Patrick's, New York City; Ted Kennedy Eulogy, 06/08/1968; martin_cj_013; Ted Kennedy’s eulogy for his brother Robert F. Kennedy, given during Kennedy’s funeral at St. Patrick’s Cathedral in NYC; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - Jackie Martin and Alice Rogers Hager on their war experiences, martin_cj_014; Interview with Gwen Sherman (CBI Theater of War) on Mediterranean and European Theaters of Operation (MTO and ETO) in 1945; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - Jackie Martin and Alice Rogers Hager on their war experiences, martin_cj_018; Interview with Gwen Sherman (CBI Theater of War) on Mediterranean and European Theaters of Operation (MTO and ETO) in 1945; 1/8 inch audio cassette (Box 50)
    - Robert Kennedy's moving speech about JFK at 1964 Atlantic City Democratic Convention, 01/01/1964; martin_cj_015; Robert F. Kennedy’s speech about his brother John F. Kennedy, fiven at the Democratic National Convention in Atlanta, GA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - Robert Kennedy's moving speech about JFK at 1964 Atlantic City Democratic Convention [edited], 01/01/1964; martin_cj_016; Robert F. Kennedy’s speech about his brother John F. Kennedy, fiven at the Democratic National Convention in Atlanta, GA; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - "Family of Man Package" special events, 10/04/1955; martin_cj_017; “Family of Man” was a photographic exhibit curated by Edward Steichen at the Museum of Modern Art in 1955.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box 50)
    - RFK 1964: Democratic Convention at Atlantic [Atlanta] [dummy copy], 01/01/1964; martin_cj_019; Robert F. Kennedy at the Democratic National Convention in Atlanta, GA; Phonograph record (Box 50)
    - RFK 1964: Democratic Convention at Atlantic [Atlanta], 01/01/1964; martin_cj_020; Robert F. Kennedy at the Democratic National Convention in Atlanta, GA; Phonograph record (Box 50)
    - Russ Morgan "Does your Heart Beat for Me", martin_cj_021; Phonograph record (Box 50)
    - Get More from Your Kenmore, martin_cj_022; Kenmore Appliance Promotional Material; Phonograph record (Box 50)
    - Get More from Your Kenmore, martin_cj_023; Kenmore Appliance Promotional Material; Phonograph record (Box 50)
    - Unknown (missing as of 7/12/2012), martin_cj_024; audiocassette
  - Memorabilia, unsorted
    - "A set of the various widths of brass used in the making of 'cylindres d'impression' from 30/100 to 260/100 mm for Pan-Am/Brussels/Paris 'Cylinder' story" (Box 27)
    - "Creative Communications" block-stamp (Box 27)
    - "Photography by Jackie Martin" block-stamps (Box 27)
    - Robert F. Kennedy Campaign buttons, never used (Box 27)
    - Eastern High School diploma, 22 Jun 1921 (Box 27)
    - Delta Gamma, Anchora Display advertisement (Box 27)
    - Documents of Longue-Sur-Mer, 1954 (Box 27)
    - French lithograph prints, set by miscellaneous artists (Box 27)
    - Times-Herald original full-page embossed printing templates and several dummy layouts, 1937-1940; 40 18x22 sheets (Box 27)
    - Government departments and agencies flip-chart pages, 12 past-up graphic sheets (Box 27)
    - Index card file box, metal, 2 drawer horizontal box containing a general and alphabetical working file of contacts, addresses, memos, and telephone numbers (Box 27)
    - Travel portfolio cases, 3 16x20x4 hard-surface; See Photographs: Entertainment: stage, theater, musicians, concerts, Photographs: Washington: politics and society, and Photographs: Various features and news photos (Oversize 1)
  - Scrapbooks
    - "Arcadian" Press books, Three 12x12 hard cover, containing promotional clippings from Arcadia Auditorium, 1927-1928 (Volume 1)
    - Biographical, 20x24 hard cover; photos of Jackie Martin and family; early photos and articles about her (Volume 2)
    - Brazil, Two 20x24 hard cover paste-up books containing photographs, notes and correspondence for trip and books that followed, 1941-1942 (Volume 3)
    - Delta Gamma, Syracuse University, 1923; 2 11x14 hard cover scrapbooks containing invitations, letters, memorabilia from college days (Volume 4)
    - Freelance career: the Beginning, 20x24 hard cover containing magazine tearsheets from Oct 1940 - Mar 1943; first edition of Chicago Sun in Washington; tearsheets: Roosevelt, Churchill (Volume 5)
    - Times-Herald, 1931-1939; 20x24 hard cover; Jackie Martin as sports editor; "Dixie's Dead End"; Conventions (Volume 6)
    - Times-Herald: "Jackie in Movieland", 1937-1939; 11x14 hard cover; autographed photos; tearsheets from Hollywood series (Volume 7)
    - Times-Herald, 1938-1941; 20x24 hard cover, containing tearsheets, clippings, and photos by Jackie Martin; "Gone With the Wind" party, 1940 Conventions, and arrival of King George VI and Queen Elizabeth (Volume 8)
    - WAAC Training, Des Moines, 1942; hard cover; contacts, articles, and documentation for Bars on Her Shoulders (Volume 9)
    - World War II photos and documentation, hard cover; preparation for unpublished book about army nurses; articles correspondence, contacts, and clippings; mounted prints signed by Jackie Martin (Volume 10)
- Photographs
  - Biographical, 12 folders; approximately 800 photographs (Box 28)
    American Photographer's Association School, Winona, Indiana (1935); in Brazil (1941-42) early years and family shots; portraits; Jackie Martin at Syracuse University (1926, 1941); with Hollywood movie stars (1937-1939); with Times-Herald staff (1931-1941); as WAAC photographer and war correspondent (1942, 1944) with famous people and others; in Paris/apartment (1950-1957); scrapbook photos
  - Ankara, Apr 1953 (Box 28)
  - Austria, 1952 (Box 28)
  - Arthur Brisbane and Walter Howey, Dec 1936 (Box 28)
  - Bloom, Sol birthday party (Box 28)
  - Justice Byrnes; funeral, 05 Jun 1936 (Box 28)
  - Chinese at Mrs. Archibald's, 1941 (Box 28)
  - Church; Times-Herald Christmas picture (Box 28)
  - Circus, 1938 (Box 28)
  - Concert-Theater, "D.C. Melody", 5 folders (Box 28)
  - Conventions; last G.A.R Parade, 1936; 1940 (Box 28)
  - DeBelt, Ambassador of Cuba, 1947 (Box 28)
  - "Dewey's shots of Vesuvius" (Box 28)
  - "Dixie's Dead End", 1936-1937; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Exhibition photos "Jackie Martin: The Washington Years (Box 29)
  - Fashion (Box 29)
  - First atlantic air flight, 14 May 1947 (Box 29)
  - Flikke, Julia, 1941 (Box 29)
  - Frink, Carol (Box 29)
  - Gold Plate Breakfast, 1944 (Box 29)
  - "Gone With the Wind" premiere in Atlanta, 1939 (Box 29)
  - Gromyko, Dec 1947 (Box 29)
  - Gustav, Carl, Prince of Sweden, 1950 (Box 29)
  - Harriman, Daisy with Maxine Davis (Box 29)
  - Harrison, Patrick, party (Box 29)
  - Hindenburg burning; Early air shots, 1909 (Box 29)
  - Hollywood stars; originals for "Jackie in Movieland", 1937-1939; 3 folders (Box 29)
  - Hoover, J. Edgar, at Convention, 1940? (Box 29)
  - Hopkins, Harry (Box 29)
  - Horse races (Box 29)
  - Hungarian president's wife (Box 29)
  - Ismay, Lord; Generals Gruenther and Ridgeway (Box 29)
  - Istanbul, Apr 1953 (Box 29)
  - Kahler, Olga, 1941 (Box 29)
  - King George VI and Queen Elizabeth, Coronation of (1937); Visit to Parliament, Ottawa; United States (May-Jun 1939); 3 folders (Box 29)
  - Lee, Gypsy Rose, 1937-1938 (Box 29)
  - Lewis, Sir Wilmott and Lady; Lord Lothian (Box 29)
  - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1940-1950 (Box 29)
  - Marshall Plan
    - Paris, 1950-1955; 4 folders
    - Kitzbeuler Horn Ski Resort, 1964-1965 (Box 29)
    - "Dutch Filmstrips no.8 and no.9, 1953; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Paris agency (Box 30)
  - McLean party, 1944-1948?; one of the last held at Friendship (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 30)
  - Nassau vacation, Dec 1938-Jan 1939 (Box 30)
  - Nelson, Donald, Saturday Evening Post, Jun 1943 (Box 30)
  - News Press Club (Box 30)
  - Nichols, Nell, 1942 (Box 30)
  - Pan American Fiesta, Woman's Home Companion (Box 30)
  - Paris (Box 30)
  - Patterson, Cissy, 1931-1941 (Box 30)
  - People, unidentified (Box 30)
  - Post, Marjorie, contacts (Box 30)
  - Perkins, Milo (Box 30)
  - Reader editors trip, Crown Collier's (Box 30)
  - Rehabilitation hospital; Civilian Air (Map) Center (Box 30)
  - Roosevelt, Alice Longworth (Box 30)
  - Roosevelt, President Franklin D. and Eleanor (Box 30)
  - San Simeon, Hearst Mansion, Ca (Box 30)
  - Scenery; airplane, beaches (Box 30)
  - Sports (Box 30)
  - Steichen, Edward, 1953-1955 (Box 30)
  - Times-Herald: "Cissy Patterson - Parties at 15 Dupont Circle", 1931-1941; shots of Cissy and Joe Patterson, William Randolph Hearst and news staff (Box 30)
  - Times-Herald: Party at San Simeon, Hearst Mansion, 1931-1941 (Box 30)
  - Times-Herald: "Cissy Patterson Parties" scrapbook, 1931-1941 (Box 30)
  - Town & Country room opening at Mayflower, Mar 1948 (Box 30)
  - Townsend, Mrs. and Mr. Lawrence (Box 30)
  - U.S. Navy (Box 30)
  - Warrenton Wedding (Box 30)
  - Washington Landmarks (Box 30)
  - Washington Society; social scene and political (Box 30)
  - Washington trial blackout, 14 Mar 1942 (Box 30)
  - Watson, General and Frances Nash (Box 31)
  - "Weekly September, 1969" (Box 31)
  - Women of Congress (Box 31)
  - Wood-Stevens, Dr (Box 31)
  - Woods-Hollingworth wedding, 1948 (Box 31)
  - World War II: France and Italy, 1944; 3 folders
    - World War II:"Enlargements from Dody McKee's negatives" (Box 31)
    - World War II: Army Nurses, 1944; mounted (Box 31)
    - World War II, 1944 (Box 31)
  - Zeppelin (Box 31)
  - Exhibition photos, 1986; 15 20x24 matted, 2 packages; 16x20 matted, 1 package (Oversize 1)
  - Entertainment: stage, theater, musicians, concerts, 16x20 some matted and mounted, in hard-surface travel portfolio case (Oversize 1)
  - Washington: politics and society - Clare Boothe Luce, William Randolph Hearst, Cissy and Joe Patterson Bernard Baruch, conventions, landmarks, 16x20 some matted and mounted, in hard-surface travel portfolio case (Oversize 1)
  - Various feature and news photos, 16x20 some matted and mounted, in hard-surface travel portfolio case (Oversize 1)
  - Marshall Plan "Photo reproduction of Exhibition prepared for European Regional Photo Conference - Hotel Tailerand, Rue St. Florentin, Paris; September, 1952", 13 20x26 mounted photo charts (Oversize 1)
  - Delta Gamma Anchora display, 13x30 mounted (Oversize 1)
  - Jackie Martin and General Patch, 1944; 12x12 autographed photo, military insignia patches, and 2 letters from General Patch mounted in 13x30 frame (Oversize 1)
  - Unidentified miscellaneous files (Oversize 2)
- Negatives and contacts
  - Assorted negatives, 1935-1965
    - Joe and Marjorie Davies party for the Barkleys (Box 32)
    - Army-Navy Women at Shoreham (Box 32)
    - Bill Calfer, sculptor (Box 32)
    - Theo Noyes (Box 32)
    - Amie and Henry Snydam, ABC Whipple, Steve Early (Box 32)
    - Jean, Bud, and Bob; Jean's father, Mr. Misener (Box 32)
    - Cape May bartender (Box 32)
    - Miss Martin, Farm and School;A Farmschool (Box 32)
    - Model ships, Reflecting pool (Box 32)
    - Girl bandit (Box 32)
    - Golden Mirror, Contestant (Box 32)
    - Opening of New Circus in New York City; John Ringling North, Mother, and Brother (Box 32)
    - Copy of "Sanctuary Poem" (Box 32)
    - Times-Herald Contax #1 [Jackie Martin] (Box 32)
    - Girl bandit (Box 32)
    - For employment agency story; Otis Black Sunday Editor (Box 32)
    - Elizabeth Arden (Box 32)
    - Christmas at orphanage (Box 32)
    - First electric train on P.R.R. Baltimore (Box 32)
    - Three girl flyers, Ruth Nichols, Louise Thayden, and ? (Box 32)
    - Lighthouse at Turkey Point, MD (Box 32)
    - Peter Carter[?], Mrs. Newton Brewer (Box 32)
    - Glen ECBD[?] PICSSIC (Box 32)
    - Labor union men (Box 32)
    - "You Cant Take It With You" (Box 32)
    - Group Health Insurance, Eye St? First Setup? (Box 32)
    - Billy Bray and Frances Woods - Dancers at the Shoreham (Box 32)